A Guide to Rockefeller University records, Corporation, Board of Trustees, Master Books FA982
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University records, Corporation, Board of Trustees, Master Books
1969-1977
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University
FA982
0.95 Cubic Feet 3 boxes - 2 document boxes and 1 half-document box
3 boxes - 2 document boxes and 1 half-document box
Conditions Governing Access
Collection is open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
File Plan
Former Classification: I 130.2-U
Arrangement
Arrangement is chronological.
Scope and Contents
The Master Books contain minutes and agendas from Board of Trustees' meetings, as well as correspondence.
- Master Books, 1969 January-May (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Master Books, FY 1970, 1969 November-1970 May (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Master Books, FY 1971 Book I, 1970 July-December (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Master Books, FY 1971 Book II, 1971 January-June (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Master Books, FY 1972 Book I, 1971 July-December (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Master Books, FY 1972 Book II, 1972 January-June (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Master Books, FY 1973 Book I, 1972 July-December (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Master Books, FY 1973 Book II, 1973 January-June (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Master Books, FY 1974 Book I, 1973 July-December (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Master Books, FY 1974 Book II, 1974 January-June (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Master Books, FY 1975, 1974 July-December (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Master Books, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 12)